# David Maldonado

301 Belcher Rd N apt. 1104•Largo, FL 33771•(727)366-8817 david.m.maldonado@gmail.com http://dave-maldonado.github.io

## Objective

To obtain a position in the Information Technology field where my problem-solving ability and drive to learn will benefit both the Company and myself.

## **Executive Summary**

More than 10 years of customer-facing call center experience in both Technical Support and non-technical customer service roles. More than 10 years of personal experience troubleshooting PC issues and two years of personal experience programming.

#### Education

### University of South Florida

expected class of 2016

- admitted for the Fall 2013 semester
- studying Computer Science
- participated in the 2013 Hillsborough Hack-a-thon and Hack for a Change events

### Hillsborough Community College

class of 2012

- graduated with an Associate of Arts and a 3.3 GPA
- took 2 courses in Java programming and a course in PC hardware
- joined Suncoast Linux User's Group (SLUG)

#### Wesley Chapel High School

class of 2001

## Selected Work Experience

## Verifone Inc. - Clearwater, FL

2012-present

• providing technical assistance to users of stand-alone credit card terminals and point-of-sale transaction software

### Marcone Part Supply - Tampa, FL

2010-2012

• assisted customers in obtaining the major appliance parts required to perform repairs

#### Macy's Inc. - Clearwater, FL

2007-2010

• provided technical support for the Macys.com website

### Safe Pest Control - Seminole, FL

2005-2007

• responsible for a route encompassing Pinellas, Hillsborough and Pasco counties

### Alltel Wireless - Tampa, FL

2004-2005

• provided technical support for the Alltel cellular network and handsets